hik-online.com 2019-07-16

# PRIVACY POLICY

Hangzhou  Hikvision Digital Technology Co., Ltd

PRIVACY  POLICY

Last Updated:  May  24 ,  2018

This Privacy  Policy explains how Hangzhou  Hikvision Digital Technology Co., Ltd ( "HIKVISION" , “we”, “our”, “us” )  as data controller  handles personal information  about you that  we collect when you use  services provided by HIKVISION  over the Internet  www.hik- online .com (“ H IKVISION Services ”) . This Privacy Policy also applies to any personal data we collect from the operation and use of products we sell while connected to HIKVISION Services (the “Products”), and any other HIKVISION Services that link to this Privacy Policy.

We may modify this Privacy  Policy at any time , provided certain provisions of  this Privacy  Policy prove to be incomplete or outdated and further provided that these changes are reasonable for you, taking into account your interests . If we make material changes to this Privacy  Policy , we  will notify you by the email address specified in your account or by means of notice on  the  websites or apps of any such changes .

You can determine when this Privacy  Policy was last revised by referring to the date it was “Last Updated” above. 

1\.  What I nformation  We Collect

In order to provide  HIKVISION S ervices  to you, we will ask you to provide personal information that is necessary to provide those  services to you. If you do not provide your personal information, we may not be able to provide you with our products or services.

“Personal information”  shall have the same meaning as “personal data”  and shall  include  any information relating to an identified or identifiable natural person ('data subject'); an identifiable person is one who can be identified, directly or indirectly, in particular by reference to an identification number or to one or more factors specific to his physical, physiological, mental, economic, cultural or social identity. Example s of personal information include  your name, email address, physical address, and payment information.

Personal information also includes information that alone cannot directly identify you, but with other information we have access to can identify you , such as product serial numbers, log data that automatically records information about your visit, such as your browser type, domains, page views, the URL of the page that referred you, the URL of the page you next visit, your IP address, and page navigation, unique device ID collected from Products and your mobile devices, data from cookies, pixel tags, and web beacons, the country and time zone of the connected Product, geo-location, mobile phone carrier identification, and device software platform and firmware information.

2\.  How We  Collect and U se  Your Information

Here are some examples of the personal information  we may collect and how we may use it :

  * W hen you create your account to use  HIKVISION Services (“Account”) ,  we will collect information including your name,  and email address . In addition, when you install and  use Products,  we will collect  certain basic information via  HIKVISION Services, such as your  product name, the  product ’s  verification code, and serial number, which are unique to the Product connected to  HIKVISION Services and associated with your Account. 
  * When you respond to our e-mails, contact our customer service, or use other customer support tools, we collect your information to provide you with support, verify your identity with your Account profile information, and confirm your Product.

We  may also use the information we collect  for the  following purpose:

  * send you reminders, technical notices, updates, alerts, support and administrative messages, service bulletins, and requested  information ; and
  * pursuant to our legitimate business interests:
    * o perate, maintain, improve, and develop  HIKVISION Services and Products;
    * personalize your experience with  HIKVISION Services and Products;
    * i ncrease the safety of  HIKVISION Services and Products – for example, for  user authentication, security protection, fraud detection, filing, and backups;
    * perform analytics and conduct customer research;
    * m anage our everyday business needs, such as auditing, administration of  HIKVISION Services, forum management, fulfillment, analytics, fraud prevention, and enforcement of our corporate reporting obligations ;
    * e nhance other information we have about you to help us better understand you and determine your interests; and
    * in the context of a corporate transaction (e.g., corporate restructuring, sale or assignment of assets, merger) and to protect our rights or property, to enforce legal notices and for the establishment, exercise and defense of legal claims;
  * meet  a legal obligation,  a court order or other binding decision (s) ; and
  * accomplish a purpose unrelated to those described in this Privacy Policy by first notifying you and, where required, offering you a choice as to whether or not we may use your Personal Information in this different manner.

3\.  Cookies and Other Technologies

We also use  cookies , web beacons, pixel tags, and other technologies to keep records, store your preferences, improve our advertising, and collect information such as log data and device data.  This allows us to better understand how you use  HIKVISION Services and Products, diagnose and troubleshoot any problems  you’re having, and otherwise administer and improve  HIKVISION Services and Products.  F or more information about cookies, please refer to our  Use of Cookies .

We may also engage one or more third party service providers to serve online advertisements on our behalf via  HIKVISION Services. They may use a pixel tag or other similar technology to collect information about your visits to sites, and they may use that information to target advertisements for our Products and  HIKVISION Services. For more information regarding this practice and to opt-out of such collection and use of this information by our third party service providers, please see  [ www.networkadvertising.or g ](http://www.networkadvertising.org/) .

4 . How We Share Your Information

HIKVISION may disclose  personal information to cloud service provider, network service provider and other service providers  on the basis of non- disclosure agreement s .

The following are the limited situations where we may share personal information:

  * We share your personal information with  HIKVISION affiliates, who are required to use that information in accordance with the purposes described in this Privacy Policy . 
  * We use service providers, vendors, technicians and other third-parties to help us process, store, and protect some of your data and otherwise help us administer our Products and  HIKVISION Services effectively, provide a better user experience, process your purchases, and increase the quality of our Products and  HIKVISION Services. These third-parties are forbidden from using your personal information for non- HIKVISION purposes and are required to protect your information in accordance with this Privacy  Policy  and applicable laws . 
  * We may provide information to third-parties if we believe in good faith that we are required by  mandatory  law to do so. For example, to comply with legal orders and government requests; response to a subpoena, or similar legal process, including to law enforcement agencies, regulators, and courts; to protect the interests of our customers and users of  HIKVISION Service; to respond to claims that any content posted or displayed using  HIKVISION Service violates the rights of third parties; in an emergency protect the health and safety of users of  HIKVISION Service or the general public.
  * We share information to protect our own legitimate business interests when we believe in good faith that we are required or permitted by law to do so. For example, we may share your personal information as needed to support auditing, compliance, and corporate governance functions; to combat fraud or criminal activity; to protect our rights or those of our affiliates and users; or as part of legal proceedings affecting  HIKVISION . 

We may also disclose non- personal information (for example, aggregated or anonymized data) publicly or with third-parties , provided those data have been  r endered anonymous in such a way that the data subject is no longer identifiable .  For example, we may share non- personal information:

  * for the same reasons we might share Personal information;
  * to better understand how our customers interact with  HIKVISION Services and Products, in order to optimize your experience, improve our products, or provide better services;
  * for our own research and data analytics; or
  * to our vendors for  their own analysis and research.

5 . Securing Your Personal Information

HIKVISION has implemented commercially reasonable administrative, technical, and physical security controls that are designed to safeguard personal information. We also conduct periodic reviews and assessments of the effectiveness of our security controls.

Notwithstanding the above, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore,  HIKVISION cannot guarantee that your  personal information is under absolute security with the existing security technology.  If you have any questions about the security of  HIKVISION Services, you can contact us  by phone  at  +86-571-8807-5998 or email  at support@hikvision.com .

6 . Accessing ,  Correcting and Retention  Your Personal Information

HIKVISION generally stores your persona l information on  HIKVISION ’s servers  which is established upon Amazon Servers  unt il you delete or edit it, or for as long as you remain a  HIKVISION customer in order to provide you  with  the most relevant offers .

Keeping your personal information current helps ensure that we provide you with the most relevant offers.  W e are ready to assist you in managing your subscriptions, deactivating your account, and removing your active profile and data.  Your personal information might not be immediately deleted, as w e are required to retain records relating to previous purchases through  HIKVISION Services for financial reporting and compliance reasons pursuant to applicable laws . In addition, because of the way we maintain certain services, after you delete certain information, we may temporarily retain backup copies of such information before it is permanently deleted. 

We will retain your personal information for  the period necessary to  fulfill the purpose outlined in this Privacy  Policy  unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by applicable law.

If you are located in the European Union, subject to limitations in applicable law, you have certain rights in respect to your personal information, such as a right of access, rectification, restriction, opposition, and portability.  In order to exercise your rights please  contact us at the contact information below.  You also have the right to withdraw your consent at all times, free of charge. You can do this by opting out from direct marketing and by rejecting the use of cookies through your browser settings.  If you  have concerns  about how we handle your personal information, you have the right to lodge a complaint with the data protection authority in your country of residence.

7 . Social Networks

We may permit others to link to HIKVISION services or to post a link to their  web site. We do not endorse these  web sites and are not responsible for other  web sites or their privacy practices.     Please read their privacy policies before submitting information.

8\.  Children’s Privacy

HIKVISION does not intend that any portion of its  HIKVISION Services will be accessed or used by children under the age of  1 8 , or equivalent minimum age in the relevant jurisdiction and such use is prohibited.  HIKVISION Services are designed and intended for adults. By using  HIKVISION Services, you represent that you are at least 18 years old , or  above  the  equivalent minimum age in the relevant jurisdiction and understand that you must be at least 18 years old , or above the equivalent minimum age in the relevant jurisdiction in order to create an account and purchase the goods or services advertised through  HIKVISION Services. If we obtain actual knowledge that an account is associated with a registered user who is  under the age of 18 years old , or equivalent minimum age in the relevant jurisdiction , we will promptly delete information associated with that account.  If you are a parent or guardian of a child under the age of  18 , or equival ent minimum age in the relevant jurisdiction and believe he or she has disclosed personal information to us please contact us  by phone at +86-571-8807-5998 or email at  [ support@hikvision.com ](mailto:support@hikvision.com) . A pare nt or guardian of a child under the age of  18 , or equivalent minimum age in the relevant jurisdiction may review and request deletion of such child’s personal information as well as prohibit the use thereof.

9 .  Global Operations 

We transfer and process your information globally  both in our own facilities and with service providers, or partners, regardless of where you use our Services.  T he laws, regulations, and standards of the country in which your information is stored or processed may be different from those of your own country .  You r registration data will  be  collected and used  or stored  by  HIKVISION , currently in the U.S. , Singapore, Brazil and Ireland . In the European  Union (E U ), we will store and keep your registration data inside the  EU in encrypted form including when we utilize a third party for storage HIKVISION put in place contractual protections, approved by the European Commission, to secure your information. A copy of those contracts can be obtained by contacting us at the address below. I n exceptional circumstances HIKVISION in China  and other countries  may have access to this content in order to provide product support services. 

1 0 . Contact Us

Please contact us if you have any questions or comments about our privacy practices or this Privacy  Policy . You  can always reach us  by phone at +86-571-8807-5998 or email at support@hikvision.com. Please pr ovide: ( i ) your name (or nickname) and preferred method of contact; and (ii) the details of your request or comment along with any corresponding website links.

Copyright@ 201 8 Hangzhou  Hikvision Digital Technology Co.,  Ltd .   ALL RIGHTS RESERVED.
